Register to The Karl Weigl Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, Series I
  - Music by Karl Weigl, I.A
    - Vocal Music
      - Songs
        - [Lieder, op. 10. O Nacht, du silberbleiche]
          - [Lieder, op. 10. O Nacht, du silberbleiche] (Box 8, Folder 280)
            English translation by Lydia Perera and Vally Weigl in manuscript.
          - O Nacht, du silberbleiche = Oh night, thou silvery pale one: op. 10, Nr. 5 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Herm. Hesse; English words by Lydia Perera and Vally Weigl. S. l.: Edition Strache, n.d., 1 score (2 p.); 31 cm. (Box 8, Folder 281)
            Pages numbered 7-8.
        - [Lieder, op. 10. Texts. English]
          - [Texts and notes] (Box 8, Folder 282)
            Also includes "Verliebt" from "Mädchenlieder".
        - [Lieder, op. 21]
          - 4 Lieder für hohe Singstimme und Klavier / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 283)
            Undated manuscript score, signed.
          - 4 Lieder für hohe Singstimme und Klavier / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 284)
            Annotated in manuscript by Vally Weigl, 1967.
        - [Lieder, op. 23]
          - Fünf Lieder / von Karl Weigl. Trieste: Casa Musicale Giuliana, 1933., 1 score (18 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 285)
            "Für eine hohe Singstimme und Klavier" -- cover.
            Includes Italian translations.
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 286)
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 287)
            English translations by Elizabeth Norman Hapgood and Vally Weigl in manuscript.
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 288)
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 289)
            English translations by Vally Weigl in manuscript.
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 290)
            Same edition, without cover.
            English translations for nos. 1-4 in manuscript.
            "Pages 2 & 14 [i.e. 15] missing" -- in manuscript.
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 291)
            Photocopy of above edition, without cover.
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 292)
          - [Lieder, op. 23] (Box 8, Folder 293)
            "Karl Weigl Memorial Fund" - stamp.
        - [Lieder, op. 23. Spielmannslied]
          - Photocopy from above edition. (Box 8, Folder 294)
        - [Lieder, op. 23. Texts. English & German]
          - [Texts] (Box 8, Folder 295)
            Includes English translations by Vally Weigl.
            Manuscript. 1941.
        - [Lieder, op. 23. Texts. English]
          - [Texts] (Box 8, Folder 296)
            English translations by Vally Weigl and Luise Haessler.
        - [Lieder aus Des Knaben Wunderhorn]
          - Vier Lieder aus "Des Knaben Wunderhorn: für vier Solostimmen und Klavier = Four songs from "Des Knaben Wunderhorn": for four solo-voices and piano / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (29 p.); 28 cm. (Box 8, Folder 297)
            Photocopy of an undated holograph score, signed.
          - [Lieder aus Des Knaben Wunderhorn] (Box 8, Folder 298)
            "or [for] 8 voices (double chorus)" -- in manuscript.
          - [Lieder aus Des Knaben Wunderhorn] (Box 8, Folder 299)
        - [Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum]
          - 6 Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum: für eine hohe Singstimme und Klavier: op. 22 / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (20 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 300)
            "Op. 22" changed to "op. 33."
          - Sechs Lieder (J. Bierbaum): für eine Singstimme und Begleitung des Pianoforte / von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (20 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 301)
          - Sechs Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum: für eine hohe Singstimme und Klavier / von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (16 p.); 35 cm. (Box 8, Folder 302)
          - [Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum] (Box 8, Folder 303)
          - [Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum] (Box 8, Folder 304)
          - [Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum] (Box 8, Folder 305)
            Composers Facsimile Edition, 1959 / American Composers Alliance (New York City).
        - [Lieder nach Gedichten von O. J. Bierbaum. Texts. English]
          See also [Liebeslieder]
          - [Texts] (Box 8, Folder 306)
        - [Lieder (1904)]
          - Lieder / von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (18 p.); 35 cm. (Box 9, Folder 307)
            "5 [changed to "6"] Lieder für eine hohe Singstimme und Klavier componirt von Karl Weigl, [text by] H. Heine, op. 4" -- added to title in manuscript.
        - [Lieder (1906)]
          - 10 Lieder von Heinrich Heine: für eine mittlere Stimme und Klavier: op. 10 / componirt von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (47 p.); 35 cm. (Box 9, Folder 308)
            Annotation in manuscript by Vally Weigl, 1967.
        - [Mädchenlieder]
          - 3 Mädchenlieder / Karl Weigl., 1 score (7 p.); 31 cm. (Box 9, Folder 309)
            Photocopy of published scores (Edition Strache), with English translations by Vally Weigl and Lydia Perera.
          - [Mädchenlieder] (Box 9, Folder 310)
        - [Mädchenlieder. Verliebt]
          - Verliebt: op. 12, Nr. 1 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Annette von Droste-Hülshoff. S.l.: Edition Strache, n.d., 1 score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 9, Folder 311)
            Publisher's no.: 31.
            Plate no.: E. St. 224.
          - [Mädchenlieder. Verliebt] (Box 9, Folder 312)
          - [Mädchenlieder. Verliebt] (Box 9, Folder 313)
          - [Mädchenlieder. Verliebt] (Box 9, Folder 314)
            Photocopy of above edition with English translation by Luise Haessler, without cover.
        - [Mädchenlieder. Es goss mein volles Leben]
          - Es goss mein volles Leben: op. 12, Nr. 2 / Karl Weigl; [text by] Walter Calé. S.l.: Edition Strache, n.d., 1 score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 9, Folder 315)
            Plate no.: E. St. 225.
            English translation by Lydia Perera in manuscript.
          - [Mädchenlieder. Es goss mein volles Leben] (Box 9, Folder 316)
          - [Mädchenlieder. Es goss mein volles Leben] (Box 9, Folder 317)
            Photocopy of above edition with English translation by Lydia Perera and Vally Weigl, without cover.
        - [Mädchenlieder. Lied des Schiffermädels]
          - Lied des Schiffermädels: op. 12, Nr. 3 / Karl Weigl; [text by] O. J. Bierbaum. S.l.: Edition Strache, n.d., 1 score (3 p.); 31 cm. (Box 9, Folder 318)
            Plate no.: E. St. 226.
          - [Mädchenlieder. Lied des Schiffermädels] (Box 9, Folder 319)
          - [Mädchenlieder. Lied des Schiffermädels] (Box 9, Folder 320)
        - [Mädchenlieder. Selections]
          - 3 Mädchenlieder / Karl Weigl., 1 score (7 p.); 35 cm. (Box 9, Folder 321)
            "Es goss mein volles Leben": Composers Facsimile Edition, c1966 / American Composers Alliance (New York City).
            Includes "Lied des Schiffermädels" and " Es goss mein volles Leben."
            English words by Lydia Perera and Vally Weigl
        - [Mädchenlieder. Texts. English & German]
          See also [Lieder, op. 10]
          - [Texts and notes], 2 items. (Box 9, Folder 322)
            English translations and notes by Luise Haessler.
            Manuscript, 1941, n.d.
            Includes a letter from Haessler to Vally Weigl.
        - [Odes (1906)]
          - 3 Oden von Nik. Lenau: für vier Solostimmen und Klavier / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (25 p.); 35 cm. (Box 9, Folder 323)
          - [Odes (1906)] (Box 9, Folder 324)
        - [Refugee]
          - The refugee / Karl Weigl; [text by ] Mary Hoxie Jones., 1 manuscript score (2 p.); 35 cm. (Box 9, Folder 325)
          - [Refugee] (Box 9, Folder 326)
            Composers Facsimile Edition, c1957 / American Composers Alliance (New York City).
            "Dedicated to the Friends Service Committee."
          - [Songs, op. 17] Composers Facsimile Edition, c1965 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (91 p.); 34 cm. (Box 9, Folder 327)
            3 songs for med. man's voice with orchestra / Karl Weigl.
            German words.
            Photocopy of an undated manuscript score with English translation by Vally Weigl.
          - [Refugee] (Box 9, Folder 328)
        - [Songs, op. 17. Vocal score]
          - Three songs for a man's voice with orchestra / Karl Weigl; English translation by Vally Weigl., 1 manuscript score (31 p.); 25 x 33 cm. (Box 9, Folder 329)
            Accompaniment arranged for piano.
            "Theodore Presser Company" -- label.
          - [Songs, op. 17. Vocal score] (Box 9, Folder 330)
          - [Songs, op. 17. Vocal score] (Box 9)
          - [Songs, op. 17. Vocal score] (Box 9, Folder 331)
            "Theodore Presser Company" -- label on cover.
          - Three songs for a man's voice with orchestra / Karl Weigl; English translation by Vally Weig l. Composers Facsimile Edition, c1958 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (42 p.); 34 cm. (Box 9, Folder 332)
          - [Songs, op. 17. Vocal score] (Box 9, Folder 333)
            "Theodore Presser Company" - stamp on cover.
        - [Songs, op. 17. Texts. German]
          - [Texts] (Box 9, Folder 334)
        - [Songs, op. 17. Texts. English]
          - [Texts] (Box 9, Folder 335)
        - [Songs, soprano, string quartet]
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet / Karl Weigl; English words by Ronald V. Smith., 1 manuscript score (17 p.); 39 cm. (Box 10, Folder 336)
            German and English words.
            "Copyright, 1953, John Markert" -- in manuscript.
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet] (Box 10, Folder 337)
            "Facsimile Edition, Copyright, 1953, John Markert" -- in manuscript.
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet, op. 36 / Karl Weigl; English words by Ronald V. Smith. New York: John Markert, c1957., 1 score (15 p.); 24 cm. (Box 9, Folder 338)
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet] (Box 9, Folder 339)
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet] (Box 9, Folder 340)
            "American Composers Edition" -- in manuscript.
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet] (Box 9, Folder 341)
            "American Music Center" - stamp.
        - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Vocal score]
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet / Karl Weigl; English words by Ronald V. Smith., 1 manuscript score (16 p.); 33 cm. (Box 9, Folder 342)
            String quartet parts arranged for piano.
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet, op. 40 / Karl Weigl; English words by Ronald V. Smith. New York: John Markert, c1959., 1 score (16 p.); 32 cm. (Box 9, Folder 343)
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Vocal score] (Box 10, Folder 344)
            "Amer. Composers Edition" -- in manuscript.
        - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Parts]
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet / Karl Weigl., 4 manuscript string quartet parts; 35 cm. (Box 10, Folder 345)
            Photocopy of an undated set of manuscript string quartet parts.
            First violin part includes soprano part, with words in English.
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 346)
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet. New York: John Markert, c1957., 4 parts; 32 cm. (Box 10, Folder 347)
            String quartet parts.
            First violin part includes part for soprano, with words in English.
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 348)
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 349)
            Same edition as above (first violin part only).
          - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 350)
            Same edition as above (viola part only).
        - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Trost]
          - Trost / [text by] Ina Seidl., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 33 cm. (Box 10, Folder 351)
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed, inscribed to Vally Weigl, Vienna, 1932 Dec 24.
          - Five songs for soprano and string quartet. I. Consolation = Trost / [text by] Ina Seidl; Karl Weigl; English words by Ronald V. Smith., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 38 cm. (Box 10, Folder 352)
        - [Songs, soprano, string quartet. Texts. English]
          - [Texts] (Box 10, Folder 353)
            Includes English translations by Ronald V. Smith
            Manuscript, n.d.
        - [Stelldichein]
          - Ein Stelldichein: für eine hohe Frauenstimme mit Begleitung von 2 Violinen, 2 Bratschen u. 2 Violoncelli / [text by] Richard Dehmel ("Weib und Welt"); Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (22 p.); 26 x 36 cm. (Box 10, Folder 354)
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed.
            "c1967."
            English translation by Vally Weigl affixed to inside front cover, typescript, carbon.
          - [Stelldichein] (Box 10, Folder 355)
        - [Stelldichein. Vocal score]
          - Ein Stelldichein = A rendezvous: op. 16 / [text by] Richard Dehmel; Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (12 p.); 36 cm. (Box 10, Folder 356)
            String sextet parts arranged for piano.
          - [Stelldichein. Vocal score] (Box 10, Folder 357)
          - [Stelldichein. Vocal score] (Box 10, Folder 358)
            English translation by Vally Weigl in manuscript and affixed to inside front cover, typescript, carbon.
        - [Stelldichein. Parts]
          - Ein Stelldichein / Ged. von Rich. Dehmel; Musik von Karl Weigl., 6 manuscript parts; 35 cm. (Box 10, Folder 359)
            Undated manuscript parts for string sextet.
          - Ein Stelldichein / [text by] R. Dehmel; von Karl Weigl., 6 manuscript parts; 34 cm. (Box 10, Folder 360)
            Photocopy of an undated set manuscript parts for string sextet.
          - [Stelldichein. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 361)
          - [Stelldichein. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 362)
            "American Composers Library" - stamp on each part.
          - [Stelldichein. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 363)
            Same photocopy as above (first viola part only).
          - [Stelldichein. Parts] (Box 10, Folder 364)
            Same photocopy as above (first violoncello part only).
        - [Stelldichein. Text. English]
          - [Text] (Box 10, Folder 365)
            English translation by Vally Weigl.
            Typescript and typescript photocopy, n.d.
        - [To Baby Christine]
          - To baby Christine: Idyl., 1 manuscript score (1 p.); 27 x 34 cm. (Box 10, Folder 366)
            "Child Asleep"--added to title in manuscript.
            For voice and piano.
            Photocopy of a holograph score, signed, New York, 1941 Dec.
        - [Wiegenlied]
          - Wiegenlied / Karl Weigl; [text by] Liliencron. Composers Facsimile Edition, c1958 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (4 p.); 36 cm. (Box 10, Folder 367)
        - [Songs. Selections]
          - [Song fragments] (Box 10, Folder 368)
            Unidentified fragments, printed and manuscript.
        - [Songs. Selections. Texts.]
          - [Song and chorus texts] (Box 10, Folder 369)
            English translations of songs and choruses.
          - [Song texts and notes] (Box 10, Folder 370)
            Unidentified fragments, typescript and manuscript.
            In German and English.
    - Orchestral music
      - [Bilder und Geschichten]
        - Pictures and tales: suite for small orchestra: op. 2 = Bilder und Geschichten / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (41 p.); 35 cm. (Box 10, Folder 371)
        - [Bilder und Geschichten] (Box 10, Folder 372)
        - [Bilder und Geschichten] (Box 10, Folder 373)
      - [Bilder und Geschichten. Es war einmal]
        - Once upon a time: from Pictures and tales = Es war einmal / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 36 cm. (Box 11, Folder 374)
          Photocopy of "Der Rattenfänger von Hameln: No. 7: Zwischenspiel".
          Title added in manuscript.
          "Was formerly intended to be used also as an intermezzo or interlude in The Pied Piper Suite" -- in manuscript.
      - [Concertos, piano, orchestra, op. 21; arr.]
        - Konzert für Klavier und grosses Orchestra, f-Moll, op. 21 / Karl Weigl; Klavier-Auszug für 2 Klaviere zu 4 Händen von Dr. Erich Simon. [Wien]: Universal Edition, c1932., 1 score (59 p.); 31 cm. (Box 11, Folder 375)
          Publisher's no.: U. E. 10.098.
        - [Concertos, piano, orchestra, op. 21; arr.] (Box 11, Folder 376)
          Theodore Presser Company (Bryn Mawr, PA) -- label.
      - [Concertos, violin, orchestra]
        - Konzert für Violine und Orchester / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (171 p.); 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 377)
        - [Concertos, violin, orchestra] (Box 11, Folder 378)
          Same photocopy, reduced in size.
          "Boosey and Hawkes Rental Library" -- label.
        - Konzert für Violine u. Orchester / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript part (27 p. ); 35 cm. (Box 11, Folder 379)
          "Boosey and Hawkes Rental Library" - stamp.
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript part for solo violin.
      - [Concertos, violin, orchestra; arr.]
        - Konzert für Violine und Orchester / von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (105 p.); 28 cm. (Box 11, Folder 380)
          Klavier-Auszug.
      - [Concertos, violoncello, orchestra]
        - Konzert für Violoncello und mittleres Orchester / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (81 p.); 37 cm. (Box 11, Folder 381)
          "Corniche" -- on title page in manuscript.
      - [Concertos, violoncello, orchestra; arr.]
        - Konzert für Violoncello und mittleres Orchester / Karl Weigl; Klavierauszug von Daniel Hernberg., 1 manuscript score (43 p.); 34 cm. (Box 11, Folder 382)
        - Konzert für Violoncello und mittleres Orchester / Karl Weigl. Composers Facsimile Edition, c1965 / American Composers Alliance (New York City)., 1 manuscript score (52 p.) + 1 manuscript part (14 p.); 36 cm. (Box 11, Folder 383)
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript score and part.
      - [Komödienouvertüre]
        - Komödienouvertüre: für mittleres Orchester: op. 31 [sic?] / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1935., 1 score (61 p.); 31 cm. (Box 12, Folder 384)
          Publisher's no.: U.E.10.263.
        - Komödienouvertüre: für Orchester: op. 32 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1935., 1 score (61 p.); 31 cm. (Box 12, Folder 385)
      - [Music for the young]
        - Spring overture: for small orchestra / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (27 p.); 39 cm. (Box 12, Folder 386)
          "Music for the Young; formerly Spring Overture."
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript score copied by W. Weissleder.
      - [Old Vienna]
        - City that was: (dances from old Vienna) / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (46 p.); 35 cm. (Box 12, Folder 387)
          For orchestra.
          Cover title: Old Vienna.
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript score copied by P. Weissleder.
        - [Old Vienna] (Box 12, Folder 388)
          Caption title changed to "Old Vienna: (dances from old Vienna)" in manuscript.
        - [Old Vienna] (Box 12, Folder 389)
          Caption title changed to "City That Was: Old Vienna" in manuscript.
          Pioneer Editions, Inc (New York City).
        - [Old Vienna] (Box 12, Folder 390)
          Caption title changed to "Old Vienna" in manuscript.
          Pioneer Editions, Inc. (New York City).
      - [Old Vienna; arr.]
        See Keyboard Music
      - [Phantastisches Intermezzo]
        - Phantastisches intermezzo: für Orchester: op. 18 / von Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (129 p.); 36 cm. (Box 12, Folder 391)
          "Leihmaterial ... B. Schott's Söhne, Mainz."
          Photocopy of an manuscript undated score.
        - [Phantastisches Intermezzo] (Box 12, Folder 392)
      - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite]
        - Orchester Suite zu "Der Rattenfänger von Hameln". No. 1. Vorspiel = The pied piper of Hamelin: The Pied Piper Suite. #1. Prelude / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (26 p.); 36 cm. (Box 12, Folder 393)
      - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Rattenzauber]
        - Der Rattenfänger von Hameln. Der Rattenzauber: 2. Bild, No. 4 = The pied piper of Hamelin: The pied piper suite. #2. The rats' enchantment / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (26 p.); 36 cm. (Box 13, Folder 394)
        - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Rattenzauber] (Box 13, Folder 395)
      - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Zwischenspiel]
        - Der Rattenfänger von Hameln. No. 7. Zwischenspiel (vor dem 3. Bilde) = The pied piper suite. #3. Intermezzo (before the 3rd act) / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (6 p.); 34 cm. (Box 13, Folder 396)
          "In the suite = # III" -- in manuscript.
      - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Ballett]
        - Ballett am Beginn des 3. Aktes des Rattenfängers von Hameln: No. 7a = The pied piper suite. #4 / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (34 p.); 36 cm. (Box 13, Folder 397)
        - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Ballett] (Box 13, Folder 398)
      - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Finale]
        - Finale: 4. Bild, No. 11 = Act 4. The pied piper suite. #5. Finale / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (44 p.); 34 cm. (Box 13, Folder 399)
          "Version without voices, chorus, harmonium."
          Photocopy of an undated manuscript score, with non-orchestral parts cut by covering with adhesive.
        - [Rattenfänger von Hameln. Suite. Finale] (Box 13, Folder 400)
          "Karl Weigl" changed to "Sentinel" in manuscript.
          "For Children's Concerts"-- in manuscript.
      - [Rhapsodies, piano, orchestra]
        - Rhapsody for piano and orchestra / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (72 p.); 38 cm. (Box 13, Folder 401)
      - [Rhapsodies, piano, orchestra; arr.]
        - Rhapsody for piano and orchestra / Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (44 p.); 35 cm. (Box 13, Folder 402)
        - [Rhapsodies, piano, orchestra; arr.] (Box 13, Folder 403)
      - [Rhapsodies, string orchestra]
        - Rhapsodie für Streichorchester (Streichsextett, d-Moll für 2 Violinen, 2 Violen, und 2 Violoncelli), op. 30 / von Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1935., 1 score (65 p.); 31 cm. (Box 13, Folder 404)
          Transcription of his String Sextet.
          Publisher's no.: U. E. 10245.
        - [Rhapsodies, string orchestra] (Box 13, Folder 405)
        - [Rhapsodies, string orchestra] (Box 14, Folder 406)
          Photocopy of above edition with holograph annotations, signed.
      - [Rhapsodies, string orchestra. Parts]
        - Rhapsodie für Streichorchester (Streichsextett, d-Moll), op. 30 / Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c1933., 6 parts; 32 cm. (Box 14, Folder 407)
          Parts for violins I and II, violas I and II, and violoncellos I and II.
          Title from caption of part for violin I.
      - [Summer evening music]
        - Summer evening music: for string orchestra / by Karl Weigl., 1 manuscript score (16 p.); 39 cm. (Box 14, Folder 408)
        - [Summer evening music] (Box 14, Folder 409)
        - [Summer evening music] (Box 14, Folder 410)
        - [Summer evening music] (Box 14, Folder 411)
      - [Symphonies, no. 1, op. 5, E major]
        - Erste Symphonie, E Dur, op. 5 / von Karl Weigl. Wien: Universal Edition, c. 1911., 1 score (185 p.); 34 cm. (Box 14, Folder 412)
          Publisher's no.: U. E. 3374.
        - [Symphonies, no. 1, op. 5, E major] (Box 14, Folder 413)
        - [Symphonies, no. 1, op. 5, E major] (Box 14, Folder 414)
          Same editions as above.
          "Sole agents, Associated Music Publishers, Inc., New York" - stamp.
      - [Symphonies]
        - [Notes, possibly about one of Karl Weigl's symphonies], 1 item (fragment of a volume cover); 34 cm. (Box 14, Folder 415)
          Holograph notes, undated.
      - [Symphonisch Vorspiel zu einer Tragödie]